<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyCityApp</string>

    <string name="city_name">Tashkent</string>
    <string name="category_type_1">Cinemas</string>
    <string name="category_type_2">Parks</string>
    <string name="category_type_3">Malls</string>
    <string name="category_type_4">Museums</string>

    <string name="cinema_name_1">Next Cinema</string>
    <string name="cinema_desc_1">
        4 halls for 63 seats each;
        Sound format Dolby Digital 5.1;
        Digital cinema projectors Christie Digital Solaria One, with a resolution of 2K;
        Screen dimensions: 5.2 × 2.2;
        A bar with popcorn, soft drinks, and snacks.
    </string>

    <string name="cinema_name_2">Anhor Cinema</string>
    <string name="cinema_desc_2">
        Sound format Dolby Digital 7.1 Surround EX;
        Digital cinema projectors Solaria One;
        Parking available;
    </string>

    <string name="cinema_name_3">Compass Cinema</string>
    <string name="cinema_desc_3">
        The Compass Cinema multiplex cinema includes six halls:
            a large hall for 230 seats, three halls for 77 seats,
            one for 66 seats and a VIP hall for 26 seats.
        There are two cinema bars, two wardrobes and a waiting room on the territory of the cinema.
        Cinema halls are equipped with Christie 2220/2215 digital film projectors and
        Eurosound acoustic system.
    </string>

    <string name="cinema_name_4">Parus Cinema</string>
    <string name="cinema_desc_4">
        4 halls for 78 seats each;
        Parking available;
    </string>

    <string name="park_name_1">Anhor park</string>
    <string name="park_desc_1">
        Parking available;
    </string>

    <string name="park_name_2">Central Park</string>
    <string name="park_desc_2">
        A green park with many attractions, a cafe on an ornamental lake, boats, a Ferris wheel, etc.
        Guarded parking.
    </string>

    <string name="park_name_3">Tashkent City</string>
    <string name="park_desc_3">
        Parking available;
    </string>

    <string name="park_name_4">Park "Yangi Uzbekistan"</string>
    <string name="park_desc_4">
        Parking available;
    </string>

    <string name="mall_name_1">Mall "Next"</string>
    <string name="mall_desc_1">
        In the Next shopping and entertainment complex, everyone can find what they like.
        In turn, it is guaranteed a high quality, good service and excellent mood.
        A wide range of unique quality goods and services.
        World brands, European standards, gourmet cuisine and much more.
    </string>

    <string name="mall_name_2">Mall "Samarkand Darvoza"</string>
    <string name="mall_desc_2">
        The best mall in town! On weekends, during working hours, when other shopping centers are already empty,
        trade is in full swing here. A lot of people, a lot of cars, everything is crowded with cars.
        But, at the same time, it is not noisy, calm and comfortable, somehow at home.
        It has everything you need for relaxation and shopping: a cafe, a cinema, a children\'s room, shops,
        restaurants, pharmacies, cafes and much more. Has its own cinema. Everything is clean, beautiful,
        comfortable. Shops are very cozy, beautiful and pleasant. Prices are lower than other stores.
    </string>

    <string name="mall_name_3">Mall "Compass"</string>
    <string name="mall_desc_3">
        The best mall in town! On weekends, during working hours, when other shopping centers are already empty,
        trade is in full swing here. A lot of people, a lot of cars, everything is crowded with cars.
        But, at the same time, it is not noisy, calm and comfortable, somehow at home.
        It has everything you need for relaxation and shopping: a cafe, a cinema, a children\'s room, shops,
        restaurants, pharmacies, cafes and much more. Has its own cinema. Everything is clean, beautiful,
        comfortable. Shops are very cozy, beautiful and pleasant. Prices are lower than other stores.
    </string>

    <string name="mall_name_4">Mall "Mega"</string>
    <string name="mall_desc_4">
        The best shopping center in the city, very conveniently located.
        There is everything you need for comfortable shopping, entertainment and relaxation.
        The store "Mega" has a huge selection of clothes, shoes, children\'s goods.
        On the territory of the mega there is a cinema where not only local films are shown,
        but also foreign ones. Many shops with branded clothing, shoes, watches, accessories, sporting goods.
    </string>

    <string name="museum_name_1">The State Museum of History</string>
    <string name="museum_desc_1">
        The State Museum of History of the Academy of Sciences of the Republic of Uzbekistan is one
        of Central Asia\'s largest and oldest research and educational institutions, dating back more than 120 years.
        The museum contains a unique collection of over 250,000 archeological,
        numismatic and ethnographic exhibits and archival materials.
    </string>

    <string name="museum_name_2">The State Museum of Arts</string>
    <string name="museum_desc_2">
        The State Museum of Arts of Uzbekistan is one of the largest museums in the Central Asia,
        which was founded in 1918 on the base of a small collection from 500 exhibits.
        These were the works of the Russian and the West-European art such as painting, sculpture,
        decorative furniture, porcelain and bronze. The most valuable exhibits of the antique and
        the early-medieval art of Uzbekistan are presented in the exposition of the museum;
        they are architectural decor, embroideries, rugs, fabrics, copper-stamping manufactures,
        golden needlework, jewelry art and others.
    </string>

    <string name="museum_name_3">Timurid\'s Museum</string>
    <string name="museum_desc_3">
        State Museum of History of Timurids opened in Tashkent on 18 October, 1996.
        The museum was placed in the centre of Tashkent for the 660-year anniversary of Amir Timur,
        and has an unusual shape, in the shape of a dome, in accordance with the style of famous locallandmarks.
        The museum building represents the synthesis of medieval, or more exactly,
        the Timurids epoch and modern architectural styles. It has a circular form with ribbed dome decorated with blue majolica,
        parapets on the roof, open aywan and orderly pillars. White marbles were used in the decoration of pillars, floor and front stairs.
        The inner side of the dome is designed in accordance with the best traditions of the eastern architecture.
        Decorated with refined ganch-carving it is covered with thin layer of gold leaf.
    </string>

    <string name="museum_name_4">Museum of railway engineering</string>
    <string name="museum_desc_4">
        Tashkent museum of railway engineering is a member of the World Association
        of technical museums on the part of railway engineering and it is one of the most interesting museums of this type around of globe.
        At present time 13 steam-engines, 18 diesel and 3 electric locomotives of historical series, produced in the last millennium,
        different kinds of cars and carriages, the most interesting samples of last century\'s repair-construction equipment are exhibited in Museum.
    </string>

</resources>